Isaac, Ikenna Magnus

Ulica Namyslowska 19, 03-455, Praga-Polnoc, Warsaw, Poland.

• Tel: + (48) 692 830 587 • Email: <u>isaacsolutions.magnus@gmail.com</u>

SUMMARY

Emerging business analytics professional with a substantial background in customer experience management ready to develop career foundation with expanding operation. Focused, strategic and well-composed with strong attention to detail, problem-solving and years of experience in payment resolutions, content & marketing operations, client operations, software development and data analytics industry. Prioritizing key tasks and strong organization skills has led me to completing tasks with acceptable target or standard before the specified time. I always strive to complete all tasks with confidence, acceptable standards, and pride. I bring a unique blend of technical knowledge, analytical expertise and business acumen to drive innovative solutions and informed decision-making in diverse professional settings and strong communication skills to deliver effective results.

RELEVANT SKILLS

- Proficiency in SAP.
- Proficiency in Microsoft 365 Admin Center, Microsoft 365 Office, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft PowerBi, Python & SQL.
- Ability to drive improvements leading to greater customer experience within the shortest possible time, higher quality, and lower costs.
- A problem-solver with high level of customer orientation, communication and attention to detail.
- Proficiency in CRM (Sales Force & Zendesk), management skills and interpersonal skill.
- Expert in productivity/collaboration tools (Slack, Microsoft 365, Discord, Miro, Smartsheet, Google Workspace, Jira, Confluence, Zoom, Notion & ClickUp), payment tools and disputes.

WORK EXPERIENCE

November 2024 - Recent

Customer Experience Expert, Teleperformance, Warsaw, Poland (On-site).

1. Provided exceptional support to customers by resolving queries related to virtual sports, bets, casino games, payment disputes, account services, and responsible gaming activities, ensuring a seamless customer experience.

- 2. Handled onboarding of new customers, including Know Your Customer (KYC) verifications, ensuring compliance with regulatory standards. Managed and maintained the customer database, ensuring accuracy and security of customer information in line with data protection policies.
- 3. Collaborated on User Acceptance Testing implementation, contributing to the successful deployment of updates and new features. Also assisted with troubleshooting gaming software for both mobile applications and websites, ensuring functionality and reliability for users.
- 4. Provide prompt and professional assistance to customers through various communication channels, while adhering to company procedures, and team performance metrics (KPIs) to achieve service excellence.

June 2024 - September 2024

Data Analyst, Gennibit, Warsaw, Poland (Remote).

- 1. At Gennibit, I conducted exploratory data analysis to discover patterns, trends, and correlations that informed strategic business decisions.
- 2. I consistently built and tested predictive models using machine learning algorithms to forecast key business metrics, helping stakeholders plan for future growth and challenges.
- 3. At Gennibit, I designed automated workflows for repetitive data analysis tasks, significantly reducing manual effort and increasing operational efficiency.
- 4. I created dynamic dashboards and customized reports using Python, Figma, Microsoft Excel, Power BI and Tableau to visualize complex data sets in a clear and actionable manner.

October 2022 - July 2024

Lead Customer Experience Specialist, Foundever, Warsaw, Poland (Hybrid).

- 1. I daily used CRM for effective customer relationship management, to view and resolve customer queries (Cases), to manage interactions effectively and efficiently with customers and potential customers, and to improve customer service. While engaging customers I employ the company's policies and ensure the set KPIs are met and surpassed for each month to contribute to the growth of the company. As a result, the number of customer complaints dropped by 27%, customer satisfaction increased by 11% and on the other hand the service level increased by 19%.
- 2. As a Customer Experience Specialist at Foundever, I leverage on team ethics, collaboration and consistent communication to deliver my tasks. As a result, our team dynamics improved, break abuse reduced, (average handling time) AHT reduced by 13% and we were able to complete projects successfully within the assigned time and resources.

3. As a Customer Experience Specialist committed to seamless customer transactions at Foundever, I resolved B2C & B2B queries by emphatically listening to customer complaints, taking ownership, and making it my responsibility to offer a solution and give options whenever possible and when it is an issue bound my capacity, I will swiftly communicate the issues to the technical team to provide accurate solutions which increased customer confidence in our organization. While working on these queries my primary priority was the customer's satisfaction, which includes providing them with information specifically tailored to their business with the aim to boost their confidence in the company. I also tackled challenges related to KYC compliance, GDPR duties, complex escalations and follow-ups.

June 2023 - December 2023

Business Analyst, **Dataline Insights**, Lagos, Nigeria (Remote).

- 1. I conducted data collection and analysis to support business decision-making, generating detailed reports using SQL, Excel and Power BI.
- 2. I collaborated with cross-functional teams and stakeholders to gather requirements, ensuring alignment with business objectives.
- 3. I identified inefficiencies in business processes while recommending implemented optimized workflows. I also relentlessly engaged in intensive training and real-world projects, honing technical skills in advanced analytics, data modeling, and reporting tools under the guidance of senior analysts.
- 4. I performed an in-depth market analysis to provide insights into industry trends, competitor strategies, and customer behavior. I also partnered with my team to deliver data-driven insights that improved business performance.

September 2021 - September 2022

Content & Marketing Strategist, **Human Guild**, San Francisco, California, United States (Remote).

- 1. I worked as a trainee with editorial, product marketing, social and creative teams to design marketing assests which in turn improved ad performance by 19%.
- 2. I contributed on the rebranding for the most prominent podcast show on NEAR; Next Creators Podcast.
- 3. I contributed to projects that raised over \$10M in funding by exploring the designs I learnt in creating high converting pitch decks, thanks to my mentor.

EDUCATION

March 2021 - April 2023

Masters in Business Administration - Management & Quality

Vistula University, Ursynow, Warsaw, Poland.

September 2010 - December 2015

Bachelors in Engineering - Mechanical Engineering

Michael Okpara University of Agriculture, Umuahia, Abia State, Nigeria.

September 2003 - June 2009

High School - W.A.S.S.C: West African Senior School Certificate

Brilliant International Secondary School, Mgbuoba NTA Road, Port Hacourt, Riverstate, Nigeria.

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATIONS

DrupalCon Prague Member Eur-tack-team: September 2022.

Certificate of National Service National Youth Service Corps: April 2016 - April 2017.

Peace and Conflict Resolution Michael Okpara University of Agriculture: April 2012.

VOLUNTEERING & CONTRIBUTIONS

Ambassador Vistula University: September 2021 - August 2022.

Member Vistula University Mentoring Programme Vistula University: September 2022 - April 2023.

Student Council Secretary General Vistula University: 2021/2022 Academic session